面倒だと思いながら 君は僕にキスをした
一边感到麻烦似的 你亲吻了我
鳴き止まない 雨は穏やか
鸣泣不止的雨稳稳落下
傘を閉じて 二人濡れた
合起伞 两人一起淋溼
 

その声に もう少し
好想要 再一下下 被你的声音
抱かれていたいな
所拥抱
愛してる？今すこし
爱著吗?虽然现在
口が止まったけど
已经逐渐不再开口
 

叫んだ想いは きっと雨と一緒に
呐喊而出的情怀 必定与雨水一同，，，，，
排水溝へ流れゆく
流进水沟之中
どれだけ素敵な 歌に乗せたって
无论搭载於 多麼美妙的歌
届かない
依然无法传达
 

When finally,the sun showed its face
最後，當天晴的時候
Your back turned to me, you started walking away
你背對著我離開，我凝視著你走遠
You didn't speak a single word,
你什麼都沒說
and I couldn't find anything to say
我也找不到什麼能說出口的話
 

I felt a pain from the blistering sunlight,
在起泡的陽光中我感受到了痛苦
and I just stood there waiting
我只能站在那裡等待
And waiting and waiting for the light to slowly
等待著你等待著光
dry my hair in the wind
風慢慢的把我的頭髮吹幹
 

I ran away from all that was certain to me
我逃離了所有肯定的我
When I tripped and fell down,the sky showed face
當我摔倒了，天空開始呈現它的臉
I didn't mind the freezing rain
我並不介意被冰冷的雨水濕透
as it soaked through everything
通過這一切的一切
And now I'll never reach you
我仍永遠無法得到你
 

And now I'll never reach you
我仍永遠無法得到你
 

(It doesn't matter where you're going, baby.)
（無論你去哪裡，這並不重要，baby）
(I couldn't live without you, baby.)
（我不能沒有你，baby）
 

叫んだ想いは きっと雨と一緒に
吶喊而出的情懷 必定與雨水一同
排水溝へ流れゆく
流進水溝之中
どれだけ素敵な 歌に乗せたって
無論搭載於 多麼美妙的歌
届かない
依然無法傳達
 

Days the earth turns to green,
當天地漸漸變成綠色
and when the sun goes down the sea
當太陽漸漸落入海平面
You will no longer be right next to me
你將不再我身邊
Even then, I can feel
即使這樣，我能感覺到
my heart whispering quietly
我的心在默默地
Pointing me where you are
告訴我你在何方




